http://www.qualityfoods.com/about-qf/privacy-statement

Current Specials
What's on Sale (By Department)
What's on Sale (Flyer)
QF OFFERINGS
A Step AboveEntertaining PlattersThe Flower StandWeddingsRocco's PizzaChinese FoodGluten Free Product List Cake CentreRecipe BookLocal ProducersDole Captain PlanetYou Chef YouClean Cart Hygiene Portal
CURRENT SPECIALS
What's on Sale (By Department)
What's on Sale (Flyer Version)
What's on Sale (List Version)
My Deals
Appy Hour
Q-CARD REWARDS
About the Q-CardRewards CatalogueMy Daily SpecialQF & ASA Gift CardsReuseable Bag ProgramThe Fine Print - How the program worksTravel Rewards with CruisePlus
Apply for a Q-Card
ABOUT QF
QF Community EventsLatest newsEmploymentSponsorshipQF HistoryPrivacy StatementLocation & HoursContact UsTerms of Use
Keyword(s):
Category:
Any
Bakery
Beer, Wine and Spirits
Bulk Foods
Dairy
Deli
Frozen Foods
General Merchandise
Presliced and Packaged Cheese
Soft Cheeses (Brie, Camembert Etc)
Crackers & Breads
Crackers & Breads
Deli Meats
Beef
Cooked Sausage
Deli Meats - presliced and packaged
Ham
Links & Sticks
Rice & Corn Snacks
Schneiders Lunch Mates (chilled)
Soup & Rice
Canned & Tetra Pak Soup
Chilled Soup
Dry Legumes
Dry Soup
Rice
Health & Beauty
Absorbent Cottons
Beef Black Angus Western Canadian AAA 21 Day Aged
Chicken (Fresh Whole and Segments)
Lamb (Fresh)
Pork
Sausage
Turkey (Fresh Whole and Segments)
Fresh Pasta and Sauce
Fresh Pasta and Sauce
Frozen Meat Case items
Beef
Lamb
Meat Pies, Sausage Rolls etc
Misc
Pork
Apples
Apricots, Cherries,
Peaches,
Nectarines and Plums
Bananas
Berries
Grapefruit
Grapes
Lemons / Limes
Melons
Oranges / Mandarins
Pears
Tropicals - Avocados, Kiwis, Mangoes, Papayas, Pineapples, etc.
Gardening
Gardening
Herbs - Fresh / Dry
Herbs - Fresh / Dry
Juice & Drinks
Juice & Drinks
Nuts
Nuts
Vegetables
Alfalfa Sprouts,
Asparagus & Artichokes
Beans & Beets
Broccoli & Brussel Sprouts
Cabbage & Carrots
Cauliflower & Celery
Cucumbers & Corn
Eggplant & Ethnic Assorted
Garlic & Ginger
Privacy Statement
Quality Foods’ Privacy Policy   Information Collected By Quality Foods When you visit a Quality Foods Website or application, some personal information, such as e-mail address, mailing address, home address, phone number, fax number, IP Address, session times, click path analysis and information about what pages you visit, is  collected by us.  By you using our services, including your use of a Quality Foods Website or application, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of this personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you participate in a voluntary survey or poll, or voluntarily provide personal preference or other personal information to Quality Foods, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of this information in accordance this Privacy Policy.
How We Use Your Information Your Personal Information collected by Quality Foods is used by Quality Foods for the purposes of communicating with you, assessing your request for products, completing your purchase of products, and for our product development and marketing analysis, including, without limitation:
Processing your request for products and completing the sale of products to you; Generate user profiles and personalize the web site to your particular interests; Customer service and evaluation the effectiveness of the Quality Foods Website; Our product and service development; Our direct marketing and marketing analysis; Facilitating your use of the Quality Foods Website and App; and
Customizing your product selection to your particular interests.
The information we collect will be confidential and will not be shared with any organizations except:
In an unidentifiable, aggregate manner, with our suppliers and research partners so that we  can provide  better service and products to you; For detecting and preventing fraud or to protect Quality Foods, or other persons, property, rights or safety; or
As required by applicable law.
We know how annoying and intruding junk e-mail can be. Quality Foods believes in positive advertising, we will not send you junk e-mail, unless you notify to us that you would like to receive promotional and sales e-mail.
We do not sell your personal information to any persons and do not provide your personal information any other persons or businesses that would use it to contact you about their products or services.   We do share unidentifiable aggregate information with our suppliers and other third parties.
The personal information collected online is stored by us for an indefinite period.
The QF App (iOS and Android) Information transmitted using the app such as your account information is transferred securely using modern cryptography (over HTTPS).  The QF Mobile app uses your phone's camera to scan items/UPC codes.  Images scanned are not stored in any way.
Your Security Recent media reports of websites being "hacked" have raised many concerns among consumers. For your security, we do not store credit card information in any way on this website.
Information about Cookies When you visit the Quality Foods Website, we place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser directory of your computer's hard drive. A cookie is a small piece of information that a web site can store on your web browser and later retrieve. The cookie cannot be read by any web site other than the one that set up the cookie.
Cookies enable this web site to recognize the information you have consented to provide and help us determine what portions of this web site are most appropriate for your personal needs. As a result, cookies give you the ability to retrieve previous image search results and view your previous invoices.
In addition, Cookies are necessary in order for us to "save" your shopping cart for 14 days so you can finish your order at a later date.
In this process we may collect your IP Address, session times, click path analysis and information about what web pages you visit.  We may use this information to better analyze the "paths" shoppers take throughout our store to find a certain item. This information, like all information submitted on a Quality Foods website, is confidential and will not be shared by Quality Foods with any persons except in accordance with applicable laws and this Privacy Policy.
We do NOT use cookies to analyze browsers after you leave our website.
If you have any comments or questions, please contact us.
Shop Online
Grocery
Meat
Produce
Bakery
Deli
Dairy
Household
Current Specials
What's on Sale (By Department)
What's on Sale (Flyer)
What's on Sale (List)
My Deals
Appy Hour
Q-Card Rewards
About the Q-CardRewards CatalogueMy Daily SpecialQF & ASA Gift CardsReuseable Bag ProgramThe Fine Print - How the program worksTravel Rewards with CruisePlus
About QF
QF Community EventsLatest newsEmploymentSponsorshipQF HistoryPrivacy StatementLocation & HoursContact UsTerms of Use
Copyright
2020
Quality Foods.
